<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--<string name="app_name">KFlight Checklists</string>-->
    <string name="title_activity_main_screen">KFlight Checklists</string>
    <string name="asset_data_dir_name">kfcl-data</string>
    <string name="preference_file_name">kfcl-preferences</string>
    <string name="first_start_name">kfcl-first-start</string>
    <string name="checklist_file_extension">.chklstpk</string>

    <!-- Main Screen Menu Items -->
    <string name="main_screen_menu_item_reload_data">Reload Crafts</string>

	<string name="disclaimer">Permissible use of this product is limited to the authorized purchaser. This product is neither approved nor endorsed by any aircraft manufacturer. It is not intended to be used a substitute for the approved Airplane Flight Manual (AFM) or Pilot\'s Operating Handbook (POH) that was originally supplied with the aircraft by the manufacturer. This product does not contain all of the information necessary to properly and safely operate an aircraft; therefore it is not a substitute for proper training in the aircraft by an appropriately-rated flight instructor. <b>NO WARRANTIES ARE EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, AND NO REPRESENTATIONS ARE MADE REGARDING THE ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN.</b> Each aircraft of a particular year, make and model may be different; therefore, the user must always verify the accuracy of the information contained herein against the approved AFM or POH for that aircraft prior to using this product. By accepting and utilizing this product, the user assumes all risk involved in its use, and agrees indemnify, defend, and hold harmless and free from liability ACPROMA LLC, and its members and affiliates, from and against any violations of law, aircraft damage, property damage, personal injury, death, or other claims and losses resulting from the use or misuse of this product, and for any errors, inaccuracies, or omissions contained herein.</string>

    <string name="google_analytics_id">UA-55704132-3</string>

    <!-- Ad Network App Keys -->
    <string name="inmobi_app_key">0138bf8a305e467d8e959462ab233b1a</string>
    <string name="ad_colony_app_key">appb38e687f388c4b7d96</string>
    <string name="ad_colony_zone_id">vz16f016050b9247fda8</string>
    <string name="ad_mob_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-9277399067724646/2499245548</string>
    <string name="ad_mob_banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-9277399067724646/9243783149</string>
    <string name="lead_bolt_app_fireworks_api_key">hHE0dM8tQI7Ul9cPXo9p38vywbHalOnU</string>
    <string name="lead_bolt_interstitial_id">897630227</string>
    <string name="native_x_app_key">22232</string>
    <string name="start_app_developer_id">110788583</string>
    <string name="start_app_app_key">210650223</string>
    <string name="super_sonic_ads_app_key">3236a385</string>
    <string name="super_sonic_ads_user_id">KFCL</string>
    <string name="tap_joy_app_key">45e2af2a-b4db-4964-b43f-a3d6a183be47</string>
    <string name="tap_joy_secret_key">t3FfaF7zFfzLN3SiD3bR</string>
    <string name="vungle_app_key">com.acproma.kflightchecklists.android</string>

</resources>
